// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
      question: "It is the formal way of asking permission",
      answer: "May",
      options: [
        "Must",
        "Can",
        "May",
        "Should",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
      question: "A obligation that express a recommendation or moral obligation",
      answer: "should and ought to",
      options: [
        "should and ought to",
        "should and shouldn’t",
        "must and mustn’t",
        "must and have to"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
      question: "It is a verb that combines with another verb to indicate mood or tense. ",
      answer: "Modal",
      options: [
        "Obligation",
        "Prohibition",
        "Modal",
        "Permission"
      ]
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
      question: "It is the prohibition that tells us against the rules.",
      answer: "Can't",
      options: [
        "Mustn't",
        "Shouldn't",
        "Can't",
        "Ain't"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
      question: "It is prohibition that is usually used when the obligation comes from the person who is speaking.",
      answer: "Mustn't",
      options: [
        "Mustn't",
        "Shouldn't",
        "Can't",
        "Ain't",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
      question: " It is prohibition that is used when we think something is good or bad idea.",
      answer: "Shouldn't",
      options: [
      "Mustn't",
      "Shouldn't",
      "Can't",
      "Ain't",
    ]
  },
{
    numb: 7,
      question: " It is the informal way of asking permission.",
      answer: "Can",
      options: [
      "Must",
      "Can",
      "May",
      "Should",
      ]
  },
{
    numb: 8,
      question: " A modal also know as ___ or ___.",
      answer: "modal auxiliary or modal verb",
      options: [
      "expressing modal or modal of obligation",
      "modal auxiliary or modal verb",
      "modal auxiliary or expression modal",
      "modal verb and modal of obligation",
      ]
  },
{
      numb: 9,
      question: "What is this sentence express? 'we mustn't scream specially when someone is sleeping'",
      answer: "Prohibition",
      options: [
      "Obligation",
      "Possibility",
      "Permission",
      "Prohibition",
      ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
      question: "This is the obligation that primarily express a firm obligation or necessary.",
      answer: "must and have to",
      options: [
      "should and ought to",
      "should and shouldn’t",
      "must and mustn’t",
      "must and have to",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 11,
      question: "You ___ throw a party.",
      answer: "Mustn't",
      options: [
        "Mustn't",
        "Must",
        "Should",
        "Can"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 12,
      question: "They ___ let her live a hopeless life",
      answer: "Can't",
      options: [
        "Can",
        "Can't",
        "May",
        "Should",
      ]
  },
  {
    numb: 13,
      question: "___ you please elaborate your claim?",
      answer: "Can",
      options: [
        "Must",
        "Should",
        "Can",
        "Can't"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 14,
      question: "__ my friend sleep over?",
      answer: "Can",
      options: [
        "Mustn't",
        "Can",
        "Should",
        "Shouldn't"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 15,
      question: "I think you ___ do this first. Ben: yes, I will do this first.",
      answer: "Must",
      options: [
        "Should",
        "Must",
        "Can",
        "Shouldn't"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 16,
      question: "What is this sentence express? 'you should validate someone’s opinion'",
      answer: "Obligation",
      options: [
        "Obligation",
        "Possibility",
        "Permission",
        "Prohibition",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 17,
      question: "What is this sentence express? 'we can't just let them die'.",
      answer: "Prohibition",
      options: [
        "Obligation",
        "Possibility",
        "Permission",
        "Prohibition"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 18,
      question: "What is this sentence express? 'can I take this?'",
      answer: "Permission",
      options: [
        "Obligation",
        "Possibility",
        "Permission",
        "Prohibition"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 19,
      question: "What is this sentence express? 'since it's already evening, can we stay here overnight?'",
      answer: "Permission",
      options: [
       "Obligation",
       "Possibility",
       "Permission",
       "Prohibition",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 20,
      question: "What is this sentence express? 'we shouldn't hurt someone'",
      answer: "Prohibition",
      options: [
        "Obligation",
        "Possibility",
        "Permission",
        "Prohibition",
    ]
  },	
  // you can make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

  //   {
  //   numb: 6,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
  //   options: [
  //     "Option 1",
  //     "option 2",
  //     "option 3",
  //     "option 4"
  //   ]
  // },
];